Curriculum vitae

Mohammad Amir Jamali

mohammadamirjamali2020@gmail.com

Mashhad, Iran 🔾

21 September, 1991 mm

GitHub 🕥

LinkedIn in

Blog ...

I hold a Master's degree in Information Technology Engineering - E-Commerce, and I have established a strong foundation in various programming languages. In addition to my programming skills, I have developed a keen interest in the fields of Machine Learning and Quantum Computing (QML). Furthermore, I possess a wealth of experience in successfully launching and overseeing startup ventures.

EDUCATION

Master's in Information Technology Engineering - E-Commerce Islamic Azad University, Birjand branch 09/2017 - 11/2019

Bachelor's in Industrial Engineering

Payam Noor University, Birjand branch 11/2009 - 02/2014

RESEARCH

- An introduction to Quantum Computing; Advantages and challenges (6th National Conference on Distributed Computing and Big Data Processing) 2021
 English version
- Comparison of the local generalization error model (LG Trader) with the exponential moving average (EMA) in selecting stocks with the highest return rate 2019 (Fourth National Conference on Applied Research in Electrical Engineering, Mechanics, Computer and Information Technology.)

Predicting Bitcoin price with Bayesian Neural Network by using COT weekly report(Master's thesis) – 2019 English version

SELECTED HONORS AND AWARDS

- Involved in finalists of UCL Hatchery Social Enterprise Award with Enviroble.Ltd (Santander Awards 2022)
- Ranked as the **second-highest** GPA among MSc students in the Computer Science faculty, with a **GPA of 3.88/4**.

EXPERTISE

- Machine Learning (Neural Networks and other Machine Learning techniques)
- Microsoft Certified IT Professional (MCITP 2008)
- Programming Languages:
 - > **JS**: JavaScript, Node, React, AJAX, NextJs, Express, Redux, Socket.io (MERN Stack)
 - ▶ PHP: WordPress Theme and Plugins Customization (Woocommerce, Stripe Connect, WC Vendor, Redis, Elastic Search, Creating Gutenberg Blocks, Elementor, WP CLI...),
 - **Python:** Web scraping (Scrapy, Selenium), Django (DRF, Redis, Celery, PyTest, Locust, Silk, Postgrsql), Cirq(Quantum Computing), TensorFlow
 - ➤ **MQL** (c++): Expert Advisor programing

WORK EXPERIENCE

СТО

Enviroble.com

University College London BaseKX

03/2021 - 11/2022

London-UK

Founder

cikit.ir

01/2020 - 02/2021

Mashhad-Iran

Founder

Class724.ir

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

05/2017 - 11/2019

Birjand-Iran

Partner

Daneshjooyar.com

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

10/2015 - 01/2017

Birjand-Iran

FAMILIAR WITH

AWS DevOps

Jenkins

System Design

Git / GitLab

Github Actions

Agile Methodologies

Travis-CI

Docker

Postgrsql

MongoDB

Microservice Architecture

RabbitMQ

kubernetes

Cassandra

Terraform

SKILLS

Collaborative

Flexibility

Studious

Positive Engagement Initiative Driven

INTERESTS

Music

Workout

Travel

Environmental Activities

Technology

LANGUAGES

English Professional Arabic Native

Farsi Native